<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>My Blog Page</title>
    <description>Travel news from all around the world</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <link>/~tomek/blog/public/index.php</link>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2021 12:38:48 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Madeira to open up to vaccinated tourists</title>
      <description>Madeira, Portugal</description>
      <link>/~tomek/blog/public/index.php/post/27</link>
      <pubDate>2021-03-02 08:41:00</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where can I travel?</title>
      <description>Which Popular World Destinations Can American Travelers Visit Right Now?</description>
      <link>/~tomek/blog/public/index.php/post/28</link>
      <pubDate>2021-03-01 18:26:16</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thailand's Tourism Sector Campaigning to Reopen by July</title>
      <description>Tourism officials in Thailand have announced a new campaign to reopen the country’s borders for international travel.</description>
      <link>/~tomek/blog/public/index.php/post/29</link>
      <pubDate>2021-03-03 05:19:30</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong Tourism Board prepares for reopening of travel</title>
      <description>The Hong Kong Tourism Board (HKTB) has announced its plan to prepare for the recovery of tourism and the resumption of international travel.</description>
      <link>/~tomek/blog/public/index.php/post/30</link>
      <pubDate>2021-03-09 11:29:06</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eurowings to boost presence in Berlin as rivals depart</title>
      <description>Eurowings is stepping up its commitment in Berlin and will open a new base at Berlin Brandenburg Airport (BER) on April 1st.</description>
      <link>/~tomek/blog/public/index.php/post/31</link>
      <pubDate>2021-03-09 11:41:40</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seychelles to reopen to tourism this month</title>
      <description>The Seychelles will reopen to tourists, regardless of vaccination status, from March 25th.</description>
      <link>/~tomek/blog/public/index.php/post/32</link>
      <pubDate>2021-03-09 11:46:46</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Escape to Greece to launch to British travellers</title>
      <description>Escape to Greece will launch this month, offering bespoke holidays to 27 destinations in the country, with over 400 hand-picked properties.</description>
      <link>/~tomek/blog/public/index.php/post/33</link>
      <pubDate>2021-03-09 12:38:48</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
